Mom?
Hey, sweetie.
What are you doing up?
Come here.
I don't like my room.
No?
That's okay. You know, you're
still getting used to it.
I can't sleep either.
What are you looking at?
Some old photos.
You want to see?
Do you know
who that is?
No.
It's me.
It doesn't look like you.
I know. But that's me.
That's your mom.
I was a kid once, too,
believe it or not.
You're old now.
How old do you think I am?
- Really old.
- Oh.
Have a guess.
Probably at least, uh, 21.
I wish
you were right.
Show me a picture
of when Dad was a little kid.
You know,
I wish I could.
But I don't think
we have any.
He's really hopeless
at keeping photos.
Show me a picture of
when I was a little kid.
You are a little kid.
You're wonderful.
You certainly didn't cry as
much as your little sister.
But she's up, so let's
go. Get some breakfast.
Billing department.
Let me play.
- No.
- I want to play!
- I'm eating breakfast!
- Billing department. Careful.
I need
a bowl, Mom.
I don't want to play soon.
I want to play now.
No, no, no, no.
Here, here.
It's too small.
Well, just make it work.
Speak to an agent.
Oh, man, what?
Every time I think
I've pulled you out,
you grow back in.
God.
Good morning, guys.
Speak to an agent!
I'm an agent.
Yeah, hello,
I would really like
to keep the old number
if that's possible.
Dude, don't eat
on the floor, Foster.
But I'm pouring my cereal.
Can I have it by the end of
the day, please, because I...
Yes. Okay. Thank you.
Foster, can you please
get up off the floor?
Cap's loose.
What is this?
Is that wax?
We have no actual fruit?
We have wax fruit?
God damn it.
And, honey, if you
wanna look at my books,
please don't leave them
all over the floor.
I didn't touch your books.
- Bye.
- See you, Dad.
See you, buddy.
You're not gonna
take the boys to school?
I can't today. Bye.
Are you gonna pick them up?
I can't.
I got a PTA meeting.
- I totally forgot.
- Why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry. Oh, no, no,
no, don't cry. Don't cry.
I'll see you guys. Bye.
Yeah, I'm looking west
Always been looking that way
I'm gonna get
it all happening
Just can't do it today
Yeah, I'm looking west
Always been looking that way
I'm gonna be somebody
I just can't be her today
Hello?
Daddy!
Hey, buddy, slow down...
- Whoa! This is awesome!
- Share it with your brother.
- Okay.
- Share with your brother.
Come watch TV with me.
All right. Look at this, babe. Nice job!
Yes, it's getting there.
Getting there?
- It looks awesome.
- Thanks.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Have you seen my box
of sheet music anywhere?
Uh, I don't know, babe.
I know we packed them.
I packed them. I know.
I just... I can't find them.
I think the movers might have
put them in the dining room.
Come here,
baby girl, come here.
It's not
in the dining room.
I've unpacked every single
box, and it's just vanished.
I can't find it.
We'll find them.
Dalton, honey?
Where are you?
Stay here. Foster,
stay with your sister.
- Dalton?
- Dalton!
Dalton!
- Hey!
- What?
Hey, hey. Hey.
What happened?
Did you fall? Did you fall off the
ladder? Honey, did you fall down?
- Yeah.
- Are you okay?
- What are you doing climbing the ladder?
- Honey...
Sorry. Sorry.
Are you okay?
What hurts? What hurts?
My leg.
All right. Can you move it? Can
you move your leg? Is that okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Oh, man.
What happened to your head?
- Oh, gosh!
- Scraped it.
Okay.
Honey, you cannot come up here,
okay? Do not explore anymore.
It's very dangerous, okay?
It's off limits now.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Okay. Okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Can you stand on it?
- Be careful.
- I think so.
I got you. Come here.
What are you doing?
You scared us, buddy.
You were just doing
a little exploring?
Yeah.
So, no more
exploring up there, okay?
Okay.
Yeah, you may be a superhero,
buddy, but you're not invincible.
You gotta be careful,
all right?
Okay.
Yeah.
Good night, sweetie.
So were you putting
boxes away upstairs?
Don't, Josh.
I just hate feeling
helpless. Sorry.
I'll figure out a way
to lock the door tomorrow.
Good.
It's dangerous, you know.
Maybe we should just
put him on a child leash.
I'll stop at
the pet store tomorrow.
I'm sorry I was pissy when
you got home from work today.
No, didn't notice.
I was trying to do
some work today and then
Cali woke up after a half hour,
and... And she wouldn't go back down,
and I just didn't
get anything done.
I just want things to be
different in this house.
Mmm.
I just had such a bad day.
I'm scared nothing
is gonna change.
It will, I promise you.
We've just got
to give it time.
Thanks for letting me take
some time to work on my music.
Come on,
I want you to do it.
I think I have
a couple of good songs.
I mean, not all of them,
but I think...
You know, there's a few
that I can do something with.
I love all your songs.
Shut up. You do not!
I do. Stop it.
Which one's your favorite?
Ooh.
You should write
a song about me.
They're all about you.
Like how cool I am.
Like,
"He's the coolest guy..."
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Shh. Quiet.
"Big muscles!"
"Really, really pretty!"
Shh, you'll wake up the baby.
Shh.
Foster, can you finish
your eggs, please?
Hey, Cali.
Can you go
wake up Dalton, Josh?
Yeah.
Hey, Mr. Sleepy-pants. Get up.
Hey, Sleepy-pants. You'd
better get out of that bed
or your mother's
gonna kill us both.
Dalton, come on, buddy. You
gotta get ready for school.
Hey. Hey.
Dalton.
Dalton?
Dalton. Dalton.
Dalton. Dalton!
There is no brain damage
that we've detected.
Technically,
yes, he's in a coma.
He doesn't react to stimuli.
He has no sleep-wake cycle.
But there's no brain trauma or
infection. His scans are all normal.
To be honest, I've never
seen anything like it.
But he can't just
not wake up. I mean...
There's got to be
something.
I'm sorry.
Okay, so...
So what do we do?
Does he stay here? Do we...
We'll conduct
some further testing.
It's only been
a couple of days.
It could take a little longer for...
Excuse me a minute. I have to step
out. I'll be back in just a moment.
Dr. Sercarz,
how long will the tests take?
Okay, so what
I've done here is
I've inserted
a nasogastric feeding tube.
To get the length of the
tube that I'm gonna need,
I measure from the tip
of the nose to the earlobe
and down to the xiphoid
process, which is here.
Then I usually mark
that off with some tape.
And then you need to
lubricate the end of the tube
that I'm going
insert about 4 inches.
And then I just
slide it in like that.
I have to make sure
the end of the tube
is curved and that
his head is a little bent,
a little bent back.
And then we usually hold it in
place with some surgical tape.
And that's it.
If there are any problems or
any bleeding, just call me, okay?
There's nothing you can do.
Nothing you can do.
I want it!
Give me it!
Give me it! I want it!
I want it! Now!
Hey, hey, hey. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
What's this?
An award.
That's today's date.
Did you get this today?
Honey,
why didn't you tell us?
I know it's hard right now, but things
are going to get better, I promise.
I'm gonna show this
to your dad.
It's fantastic.
I'm scared, Mom.
Scared of what?
Dalton.
Can I change rooms?
Why would you want
to change rooms?
I don't like
when he walks around at night.
Something really weird
happened to me today.
Huh. What?
I heard this noise
coming from Cali's room.
It was on the baby monitor.
It was like voices.
And I ran up here and I had a
look, but there was no one in there.
It was
probably just interference.
Those things are always picking
up somebody else's signal.
I don't know.
It sounded so clear.
It was like
this whispering.
It was...
It scared the hell out of me.
I was at the piano, and I
could hear it on the monitor,
and I turned up
the volume and...
Who the hell is that?
Hold on.
Stay here.
Who is it?
Jesus.
Hello?
Oh, my God!
Josh! Josh! Josh!
Please. Someone's in Cali's
room! Someone's in Cali's room!
There's someone there!
I saw somebody!
He was standing right there!
- There's nobody here.
- I saw someone!
Okay, take her, get Foster,
go in Dalton's room.
- Foster!
- What's going on?
The alarm's gone off!
God damn it!
Thanks, guys.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey, honey. It's me. Um...
They just told me,
I've got to...
I'm gonna have to
stay late tonight to...
I gotta grade some tests, and
it's gonna be a while so, um...
You don't have
to wait up, okay?
I'll be home as soon as I can.
I love you.
Did he respond to
any of the new tests?
No. No, he didn't.
But we have to
give it time.
I've seen coma patients with
a much longer inactivity time
suddenly start
making noises.
He's not in a coma. They
don't know what to call it.
They don't know
what to do with him,
so they've just given up.
I feel like
the universe is just
trying to see how far
I'll bend before I break.
Well, the universe picked a
fight with the wrong chick.
That's okay. I got it.
Thank you.
Okay.
Josh, where are you?
I need you to come
home now, please.
It's 10:30.
Mmm-hmm.
You've been coming home late
every single night.
In all the years you've worked at the
school, you've never had to do that.
Why all of a sudden
are you staying back late?
You know,
I don't like it either.
I was grading tests.
I mean...
What choice do I have?
- I've got to pay Dalton's bills.
- Josh.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared and...
He's my son, too.
You don't understand.
I'm scared for Dalton.
I'm scared of this house.
There's something wrong
with this place.
I'm not imagining it.
I can feel it.
It's like a sickness.
Ever since we've moved in,
everything's just gone wrong.
You think
our house is haunted?
I don't think it.
I know it.
Things move around
in here by themselves.
I walk into the kitchen at night to
get a drink, I can feel eyes on me.
I can't be in there
alone anymore.
I need you.
But you're never here.
Where are you?
I told you.
I was grading tests.
That's not what I mean. You're
not here with me in this situation.
You're just avoiding it,
like everything stressful, whether
it's this or parking tickets.
Oh, God.
Stop saying that, okay?
I don't avoid
stressful situations.
I'm just dealing with it
in my own fucking way.
Fine. Deal with this!
Jesus.
Oh, God.
Josh?
Josh.
Renai?
Renai!
What, what, what?
What is it?
There's someone here.
There's someone
in the room!
He was right there,
I swear!
Don't you dare
not believe me.
Please.
Please, believe me.
I swear he was right there.
I do, I do.
I do believe you.
I just don't know
what you want me to do.
I want to leave. Please.
I want to leave this house.
I can't spend
another night here. Please!
Please, help me!
Okay, okay, okay.
We're going.
Lorraine, please, you shouldn't be
doing any of this. Just sit down.
I'm perfectly capable
of putting a few things away.
I did it for Josh
his whole life.
I know,
but I feel terrible.
I think it's you who should be
sitting down by the looks of it.
I can't believe you got Josh
to hold still for a photo.
What I can't believe is that we
are doing this all over again.
Ridiculous.
You must think
I'm crazy.
Nobody,
not me or anybody, knows what
you're going through right now.
Whatever you have to do
to get through it, do it.
And you don't have to
apologize for anything.
Thanks.
Dalton?
Your faith can help.
Trust it, you know.
Hello.
Josh.
This is the first line
of a joke, right?
A guy comes home to find
his wife with a priest.
Uh, this is Liam Martin.
- Nice to meet you.
- He's actually a very old friend of mine.
- Huh.
- This is my husband, Josh.
What's going on here?
Thank you. I should be going.
Thank you so much.
Thank you
so much for the tea.
This thing from
the other house
has followed us here.
I saw something today.
I thought it was a little boy.
I followed it into Dalton's room.
But it wasn't a child.
It was something else.
So what? You just brought
a priest in to get rid of it?
I didn't know
what else to do, Josh.
Come on, Renai.
When's the last time
you went to church?
What's happening
to Renai is real.
I've seen it for myself.
I came today
because last night
I had a dream
about this place.
I was in this house,
but it was late at night.
I was afraid.
I went into your bedroom,
but you were both asleep.
I knew I was asleep
in the dream,
but I could feel
that someone was awake
in the house.
I went into Dalton's room.
There was something
in there with him.
It was standing there
in the corner.
I asked it, "Who are you?"
And it said it was a visitor.
I said, "What do you want?"
It said, "Dalton.' '
I can still hear that voice.
What? What?
It's here!
What?
Jesus!
Oh, my God!
Okay. He's okay.
Please! Please,
help him! Please!
I know someone who can help
if you're willing to ask.
I'm Specs.
This is Tucker.
- I'm Renai. Hi.
- Hi.
You must be Josh.
Yeah. Hi.
That wasn't psychic. Elise
already told me your name so...
Where is Elise?
She sent us ahead to do
some preliminary tests.
Helps weed out
the nut jobs.
Hmm.
What is that?
It's
a Trifield meter.
Measures DC fields
and the natural
electromagnetic environment.
Yeah, sometimes old wiring
can leak into the atmosphere.
It causes hallucinations,
changes in energy.
It's a little more important
than that, but whatever.
The tech stuff's not really
relevant to you guys anyway.
It's all very relevant,
actually.
What?
Starfleet Series One.
It's hard to find.
Should have
kept it in its box.
This device measures
changes in UV light.
I make all this
equipment myself, you know.
It's impressive.
Thanks.
It's not that hard if you
know what you're doing.
Yeah, that one's
basically a modified toy.
I'm gonna need some time
alone to concentrate.
This field is... Look, the
body is made up of energy.
Where does that
energy go when we die?
We can call Elise.
Now.
I wasn't sure the doorbell
was working. I'm sorry.
- That's fine. Come on in.
- Thank you.
Mrs. Rainier?
No, Mrs. Rainier is my
mother. Just call me Elise.
- I'm Josh.
- I knew that.
You've grown
since I last saw you.
- Since you last saw me?
- Mmm-hmm.
Your mother and I have
been friends a long time.
Oh.
Well, hello.
This is my wife, Renai.
How do you do?
Hi, thank you for coming.
Thank you for having me.
Can we get you
anything, Elise?
Oh, no, I'm fine,
thank you so much.
We took Trifield and EMF
readings of the whole house,
all the wiring, alarm
clocks, radios, toasters,
TV, record player, fuse box,
nothing went off
the charts except for the...
And the previous home?
Um, Tucker hadn't
monitored that yet.
You know what?
Don't even sweat it.
I'll make
myself available.
I'll get on that
this afternoon.
Yeah, but I'll have
to come, too,
because who's going
to operate the equipment?
Well, strictly,
I could do it without...
- Yeah, but I need to oversee...
- Yeah, but it's not...
That's fine, gentlemen.
I don't think bad wiring
is the problem here.
Um, may I walk
through the house?
- Sure, of course.
- Thank you.
Your other children
are with Lorraine, right?
Yeah, they are.
Steven, do you have
your sketchbook?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Good. 'Cause
we're gonna need it.
What do you
need that for?
Um, she tells me what
she sees, and I draw it.
It's the most important
part of her process.
- That's debatable.
- It's not debatable.
It is, but whatever.
Leave the light off.
Hey, Dalton.
You are a very
handsome boy.
Your mom and dad are here,
so don't you worry.
What? What...
The face...
What?
Blood red face.
Black...
Black arms. Black legs.
Black body.
Slow down.
His feet are black.
His legs are black.
Slow down.
What is it?
Oh, my God.
And pitch black eyes.
They're like two dark holes.
He has hooves for feet.
What?
And long
spidery fingernails.
Elise, what's...
Hey, what is that?
I'm not sure if you're
ready to hear this yet,
but unfortunately, I can't waste
any time easing you into it.
I want you to know,
this is what I believe,
and it may contradict a previous
medical diagnosis, but...
You called me here,
and I'm taking that
as an acceptance
of my readings. Yes?
Yes, go on.
Your son isn't in a coma.
Falling off a ladder
had nothing to do with this.
His physical body's here.
But his spiritual body is not.
And the reason
these disturbances,
they followed you
to a new home,
is because it's not
the house that's haunted.
It's your son.
I don't understand.
Have you ever heard
of astral projection?
Yes. It's out of body
experience or something?
I like to call them travelers.
You see, these are people with the
ability to leave their physical body
and to travel to different
places in astral form.
Now, Dalton,
he is a very accomplished
astral projector.
He's been doing it in
his sleep for a long time.
He has been since
he was very young.
And he's unafraid because
he thinks they're dreams.
And it's that
very lack of fear
that has led him
to travel too far.
And to become lost.
Lost?
Lost where?
In a place that
I call the Further.
What? What does that mean?
The Further is a world
far beyond our own,
yet it's all around us,
a place without time
as we know it.
It's a dark realm filled with
the tortured souls of the dead,
a place not
meant for the living.
That's where Dalton is.
And the problem is that
with his astral body gone,
he's just left us with a
physical body, an empty vessel.
And there are entities that know
this because they can smell it.
That's why they're
gathered around him.
Are these the things
that I've been seeing?
They're all trying to get
inside of his physical body
simply because they...
They crave life,
the chance to live again.
But there are other entities
who are malevolent
and have a more
insidious agenda.
And then, there's this.
A demon who seeks Dalton's
body for one reason:
to cause pain to others.
He is so desperate
to possess Dalton,
and he's the closest of all the
entities to getting inside of him.
What do you mean
the closest?
Because these entities, they can't
just walk into the bodies of the living
anytime they please.
To cross over
from their realm,
it takes time.
It takes energy.
But the longer that
Dalton's astral body
is kept away from his physical
body, the weaker the link gets.
The easier it is
to possess him.
Is there anything we can do
to bring Dalton back?
There's something
we could try.
It's a little unorthodox.
But I would need
your complete trust.
No, no, no. I'm sorry,
this has gone too far.
What? No, please, Josh. You
said you would give her a chance.
I have given her
a chance, honey,
but I can't have somebody
coming into our home
and telling us the reason
our son is in a coma
is because his soul
has floated off
somewhere
in another dimension.
We're gonna bring her
all the way here
and not even consider
what she's saying?
I did this to make sure you could
feel at ease. And if it helped, great.
I've listened to the dog and pony
show. I have seen the drawings.
But to bring
Dalton into it, no.
But why is our son
still in a coma?
Why can't the doctors tell us
what is wrong with him?
How did the voice of reason
become the bad guy here?
Don't you see, Renai? You
want to believe. Anybody would.
You don't believe me!
I moved houses for you.
What do you mean, I don't believe
you? I'm on your side here.
But this, this is
dangerous and exploitative.
You guys come into the home
of a seriously ill child,
and you make some tenuous
connection between him
and the images my wife
is seeing, and voil?
Tears validate your power, and thank
you very much, that will be $600 please.
- Thank you for coming.
- Please. Please.
- Thank you. No, I really understand.
- Please.
Thank you for your
hospitality. Good luck.
Oh, Jesus!
Sorry to waste your time.
Where are you, buddy?
Did you go somewhere?
No.
No, you're right here.
You are right here.
Can you hear me?
I know you can hear me, but
you gotta show me, okay, buddy?
You gotta show me
that you can hear me.
Okay.
What's most important is that you
realize no two attempts are the same.
I'm going to be completely
honest with you about the results.
If there's no dialogue
established, I'm gonna tell you.
These still cameras are rigged to
pick up any changes in the atmosphere,
both electrical
or temperature-wise.
Don't be alarmed
if they go off.
You're gonna see a lot of confusing
things, things you don't understand.
But do not question them
and do not speak in any way.
I want you to know whatever
I say when I'm in tune
is going to be at a very low
volume. You won't hear any of it.
But Steven's
gonna write it down.
He's going repeat it
for you. Okay?
Dim the lights, please.
We are calling
out to you, Dalton.
Tell us you're safe.
Tell us where you are.
Dalton.
Can you hear us? Answer us.
Who's there?
Dalton, it's your
mother and father.
We've been
searching for you.
Where are you?
I can't see in here.
Dalton... Dalton,
you don't need to see.
Follow my voice.
Follow my voice, Dalton.
Dalton. Why aren't you...
Why aren't you
talking anymore?
Dalton?
If they hear me,
they'll hurt me.
Who will hurt you?
Who will hurt you, Dalton?
The man
with
fire
on his face.
Dalton.
Dalton, can you
find your way out?
There is
no way out.
Follow my voice, Dalton.
Follow my voice.
Be quiet.
They'll hear you.
They won't hear me, Dalton.
Follow my voice.
They heard you.
Oh, my God.
Mommy and Daddy.
Help. Help.
Help me, help me, help.
Dalton?
You bitch.
Specs!
Leave this vessel!
Leave his body!
Tucker, turn on the light!
Leave this body now!
Come here, Dalton.
Son. Come here.
- He's alive. He's alive, oh, God.
- He's alive? Jesus.
- Honey.
- Oh, God.
Three cameras. Around
the clock. We got nothing.
But I did find this
on the video.
Take a look.
You see that?
I went through it.
Frame by frame
by frame.
Oh, my God.
- Who's that?
- I'll get it.
Hi, Lorraine.
Mom, what are you
doing here?
I asked your mother
to come over.
I called her immediately
after the session.
Why?
There's something
we must talk about.
Lorraine, have a seat.
Go on. Tell him.
Tell me what, Mom?
The reason
I knew to call Elise in this situation,
the reason I know her so well,
is because I called her
myself once, years ago,
to help you.
What are you
talking about, Mom?
It's no accident that your
son is a gifted traveler.
The ability was
handed down to him.
By his father.
Me?
No, I don't do...
I can't do that.
When you were about eight,
you suffered night terrors,
these awful fits
of pure fear.
You were terrified
of an old woman
you said used to come
visit you at night.
I dismissed
your stories. I...
I told you to grow up.
And then
I saw her for myself.
At first, I thought
it was a camera problem.
And then I saw her again.
In each photo,
she got closer
and closer
and closer to you.
Finally, I was so
frightened, I found Elise.
Do you remember
any of this, honey, do you?
No. I don't.
Suppressing your memory and
your ability to astral project
was the only way to stop her
from getting into you.
But in the back
of your mind,
you're still afraid to have
your picture taken, aren't you?
I kept those photos
hidden from you ever since.
I advised Lorraine
to hide them,
to stop taking your picture,
to just let you forget.
Who is she?
A parasite.
She befriended
your astral body
and then drew you out
into the Further,
just as Dalton
has been drawn out.
I'm so sorry, Josh.
I didn't want to make you
remember all this.
I do it for
the sake of your son.
Your son is out there.
And you are the only one
that can bring him back.
And with what
we saw tonight,
I would say he doesn't have
much time left to wait for you.
Okay.
You've always been
stronger than me.
You can do this.
- I love you.
Please come back.
Remember
why you're traveling
and keep one foot
in this world.
Do not draw
attention to yourself.
If they realize
you are not one of them,
they will come for your
physical body in this world.
Ready?
Yeah.
I don't know what
I'm ready for, but... Okay.
Close your eyes, Josh,
take a deep breath, and relax.
With each breath,
let the life around you
fade into the background.
Just listen to the ticking
of the metronome.
Focus on the spot in the
center of your forehead.
The universe is deathless.
It is deathless because having
no finite self, it stays infinite.
A sound man,
by not advancing himself,
stays the further
ahead of himself.
It's useless. I have
no idea what I'm doing.
Now you're outside.
Let my voice be your guide.
Keep a steady stride.
Into the Further you go.
Dalton.
He's in.
Dalton!
Hello?
Wait!
I'm looking
for my son Dalton.
Dalton!
Where's my son?
Tell me where my son is.
Please.
What's happening to him?
Jesus.
Help him, Elise! Please!
You're stronger
than they are, Josh.
You can beat them. You are
stronger. You are the one alive.
Get away from me!
Dalton!
Daddy?
- Oh, God! Buddy!
- Daddy!
- Oh, my God! Oh, buddy.
- Daddy.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, buddy, it's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. Oh, God.
Daddy, look. I'm chained.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Face me, buddy.
Face me. Come here.
We'll get you out. We'll
get you out, buddy, okay?
Daddy's here.
What? What?
Oh, God. Okay.
It's okay.
Listen to me. Look at me.
None of this is real, okay?
This is not real.
Look at me.
Look at my eyes, buddy.
None of this is real.
We're going to go home, okay?
You gotta help me.
There's one.
Oh, my God, Dad.
He's looking.
Come on, baby. Stay here,
baby. Come on, stay with us.
Daddy!
He's made contact.
Grab the light!
He found your son.
I know it.
Well, then wake them up,
for God sake!
I can't.
He needs to find us.
I'm scared, Dad.
No! Stop!
Please, Elise,
do something!
Renai, you must
call out to him.
Josh. Josh.
Follow my voice!
Follow my voice, honey.
Get away! Get away!
Come back to us!
Follow my voice, Josh.
Daddy! Listen,
I think it's Mommy!
Josh, come back to me.
Follow my voice.
Josh, follow my voice.
Follow my voice, Josh.
Follow my voice.
There's something in there!
In there!
Elise!
Steven, Lorraine,
go check on Dalton.
- What?
- Go check on Dalton.
- Go check on Dalton now!
They're crossing over
into our world.
- Elise!
- Tucker!
No, you have to shine
the light on Josh.
Come on!
Let's go around back.
Shine the light on Josh!
On Josh!
Tucker, on Josh!
You've got
to call him back!
Josh!
Josh! Josh! Come back
to us, Josh, please!
Josh! Josh!
Come back, please!
Come on, Dad! Come on,
he's right behind us!
We have to go!
I'm right behind you! Go!
You.
What do you want from me?
I'm not scared of you.
I'm not scared
of you anymore.
You can get away from me.
Get the hell away from me!
Get away from me!
Leave me alone!
Please, please, please!
Come back to us!
Follow my voice!
Please, honey!
Josh, come back!
Come back to us!
Get the hell away from me!
Please, Josh, please,
come back to us, please!
Follow my voice!
Follow my voice! Please!
Josh, please!
Come back, please!
Leave me alone!
I've got Dalton.
He's awake!
Oh, my boy!
He's okay! He's okay!
We did it, buddy.
You're back. You're back.
Dude, I got some
amazing shots.
You're gonna write a book,
and my photos are gonna be
the main selling point.
Not the main selling point, but
they'll definitely be important.
They will be important.
A picture's worth
a thousand words.
Yeah, but words are worth
a thousand words, too.
You're really hungry,
aren't you?
And I'm tired, too.
You're tired?
No, you can't be tired.
Yes, I can.
No, you've been asleep for far
too long. And you know what?
I'm never letting you
go to sleep again.
You showed me a new world.
No, I didn't.
You've been there
before, remember?
Well, let's hope
I forget again.
Guess I don't need
these anymore.
What?
Nothing.
I'm gonna
get rid of these.
All right.
Why did you do that?
Why would you do that to me when
you know how I feel about that?
Why? Why?
Why? Why? Why?
No, you're not tired.
In fact, you're never going to
sleep again. You have to stay awake
...for the rest of your life, with me.
- No.
Why? Why? Why?
You bitch!
Can you watch him,
Lorraine?
Sure.
Elise.
Josh! Josh!
Josh, where are you? Josh!
Honey, please... Josh!
Josh?
Oh, Jesus.
Renai,
I'm right here.